photocamel.com 2018-08-07

# Privacy Policy - PhotoCamel - Your Friendly Photography Forum

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on PhotoCamel.com, you may be asked to enter a user name, password, and e-mail address. We have no access to the password you create. For access to certain parts of PhotoCamel, you may be asked to provide your real name and date of birth. This information is not transferred to any third party. You may also visit PhotoCamel.com anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on PhotoCamel.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).

To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).

To process transactions.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering a purchased product or service requested or for providing a contest sponsor with the information necessary to contact you to arrange for delivery of a prize. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

To send periodic e-mails.

The e-mail address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider's database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems.

After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [website's privacy policy](https://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at the e-mail address below.
